Advertise your product or brand here contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Who are the real-world Illuminati ? Find out @ saveanilluminati.com
Okay, Ray,
Muito bem, Ray,
you are an incarcerated volunteer in the Spider head clinical trial program.
יs um recluso voluntבrio no ensaio clםnico Cabeחa da Aranha.
Before we begin, I need your permission to administer G-46.
Antes de comeחarmos, preciso de permissדo para administrar G-46.
- Drip on? - Acknowledge.
- Aceitas? - Consinto.
What was the ghost's favorite fruit?
Qual era a fruta favorita do fantasma?
Boo-berry.
Bu-va.
No shit, that's funny.
Essa teve piada.
What did the magician say to the fisherman?
Porque י que Noי nדo podia pescar na arca?
Pick a cod, any cod.
Sף tinha duas minhocas.
What do you call cheese that isn't yours?
Como fica o queijo depois do ginבsio?
Nacho cheese.
Fica "roqueforte".
All right, Ray, Ray, these next ones aren't jokes, more just facts, okay?
Ray, as prףximas nדo sדo piadas, sדo factos, estב bem?
Oh, yeah?
A sיrio?
In the 1994 genocide in Rwanda, over 800,000 people died.
No genocםdio de 1994, no Ruanda, morreram mais de 800 mil pessoas.
You are serving…
Cumpres…
You're serving four consecutive life sentences
Cumpres quatro penas perpיtuas consecutivas
without the possibility of parole.
sem possibilidade de condicional.
Ray, thank you. You're free to cruise, buddy.
Ray, obrigado. Podes ir, pב.
Another beautiful morning, friends,
Outra bela manhד, amigos e vizinhos.
time to rise and really shine.
ֹ hora de acordar e levantar.
As volunteers in the Spider head Penitentiary and Research Center…
Como voluntבrios nesta Penitenciבria e Centro de Pesquisa,
no abuse, physical, verbal, or otherwise and label your food in the fridge.
nada de agressץes fםsicas ou verbais e etiquetem a vossa comida.
Jeff, please report to the dock for remote field testing.
Jeff, dirija-se ao cais para teste de campo remoto.
Okay, Jeff, we have a new compound for you today.
Jeff, hoje temos um novo composto para ti.
- Drip on? - If it's N-31.
- Aceitas? - Se for N-31.
Hilarious, N-40. Acknowledge?
Hilariante, N-40. Consentes?
Acknowledge.
Consinto.
Yeah, whenever you're ready, Jeff.
Quando quiseres, Jeff.
It's really nice.
ֹ muito bonito.
Oh, boy. Okay if we pep up your language centers, Jeff?
Podemos aprimorar os centros de linguagem, Jeff?
Drip on?
Aceitas?
- Sure. - Acknowledge?
- Claro. - Consentes?
Oh, sorry. Yeah, acknowledge.
Desculpa. Sim, consinto.
Hey, sorry, I'm late.
Desculpa o atraso.
Party's here.
Chegou a festa.
Such a creep.
Que parvo!
- Where you been? - Field trip.
- Onde estiveste? - Excursדo.
Oh, right, your phone call with Emma.
O telefonema com a Emma.
No, uh, drug study.
Nדo, o ensaio farmacolףgico.
N-40, I think.
N-40, creio.
They have everyone on these field trips but me.
Metem toda a gente nessas excursץes menos a mim.
You're still new.
Ainda יs nova.
I'm not that new. You know, I'd love some sunshine.
Nדo sou assim tדo nova. Adorava apanhar um pouco de sol.
Can I help you with the…
Posso ajudar-te com…
Nectarines and prosciutto?
Nectarinas com presunto?
What you gonna help with? I'm done. You're late.
Com o quך? Jב terminei. Chegaste tarde. Abre.
Enjoy that. Get it all.
Desfruta. Sente o sabor.
- Yeah. - It's really good.
- Sim. - ֹ muito bom.
- Good, right? - I hope they keep you on snack.
- Nדo י? - Espero que continues na cozinha.
I always said they wasted your talents on janitorial.
Sempre disse que eras um desperdםcio nas limpezas.
Don't be too sure about that. I've got a bit of a scrub fetish.
Nדo te fies nisso, adoro esfregar.
- Okay. - Hey…
- Certo. - Olha…
- Did you notice we kinda... - Finish each other's sentences?
- Jב reparaste que nףs… - Terminamos as frases um do outro?
I was gonna say, need new bowls.
Ia dizer que precisamos de taחas.
Uh…
Entדo, como foi o N-40?
Flowers didn't grow…
As flores nדo cresceram…
They were sculpted. Painted.
Foram esculpidas. Pintadas.
I mean, I would tell you about it, but I'm just coming down off the...
Eu contava-te,
- Verbaluce. - Yeah.
- Verbaluce. - Sim.
That tip-of-the-tongue feeling when you can't find the right word
Aquela sensaחדo de teres a palavra na ponta da lםngua,
and you feel like you'll never find the right word again?
mas parecer que nunca mais a encontrarבs?
Yeah.
Sim.
Well, you're cute when you're stupid.
ֹs giro quando יs burro.
Okay, but it sucks because today was the day that…
Estב bem, mas י uma merda porque hoje era o dia em que…
There was something that I was gonna tell you today, Lizzy.
Hoje ia dizer-te uma coisa, Lizzy.
Okay, well, we got time.
Estב bem.
Yes, we do.
Sim, pois temos.
All we've got is time.
Tudo o que temos י tempo.
Okay.
Pronto.
What you know about this?
O que percebes disto?
You know nothing about this.
Nדo percebes nada disto.
So, to sum up…
Resumindo…
I love it.
Adoro.
It's beautiful.
ֹ lindo.
- Where do you wanna take me? - Hmm.
Aonde me queres levar?
What about that island, you know, the one where they make water?
Que tal aquela ilha, aquela onde fazem בgua?
Fiji?
Fiji?
Fiji.
Fiji.
- I'll take you to Fiji. - Thank you.
- Eu levo-te lב. - Obrigada.
Just need a little money.
- Sף preciso de algum dinheiro. - Vamos ao aniversבrio do Mark?
It was Tuesday, but he's a celebrate-all-week motherfucker. Please?
Foi na terחa, mas celebra a semana toda.
You two go have fun. I'm gonna stay here. Okay?
Vדo divertir-se. Eu fico aqui. Estב bem?
- Miss you. - Miss you more.
- Terei saudades. - Terei mais.
You cool to drive?
Consegues conduzir?
Ice cold.
Na boa.
Oh, Jeff, Jeff, Jeff!
Jeff!
Sorry, I'm late, Mr. Abnesti.
Desculpe o atraso, Sr. Abnesti.
I'm gonna retire the day you call me Steve.
Reformo-me quando me chamares Steve. Nדo estבs atrasado.
Heather, on the other hand…
Jב a Heather…
Yeah, speak of the devil.
Fala-se no diabo…
Sorry.
Desculpem.
All right.
Muito bem.
Oh, how rude of me. Jeff, Heather. Heather, Jeff.
Que indelicado. Jeff, Heather. Heather, Jeff.
For the record, either prior to or during your incarceration here at Spider head,
Para o registo, antes ou durante a vossa reclusדo aqui na Cabeחa da Aranha,
have you two ever spoken?
alguma vez se falaram?
- No.
- Nדo.
Ever interacted in any way?
Tiveram algum tipo de interaחדo?
Did I not just say no?
Nדo acabei de dizer que nדo?
No.
Nדo.
So, what do you think?
Entדo, o que achas?
Who are you asking?
A quem estב a perguntar?
I'm asking both of you. Let's start with Jeff.
Aos dois. Vamos comeחar pelo Jeff.
Yeah, she seems nice.
Ela parece simpבtica.
You like that word, but no, I mean, how attractive is she?
Gostas dessa palavra, mas nדo. Quדo atraente י?
What, Steve, you can't see it for yourself?
Nדo consegues ver, Steve?
Can you shut up, please? I'm asking Jeff. How's she looking?
Calas-te? Perguntei ao Jeff. Como י ela?
- A scale of one to ten? - Um…
Numa escala de um a dez?
Yeah, she's a seven and a half.
Pois, ela י um sete e meio.
And, Heather?
Heather?
He's all right. A five on a good day.
Nדo י mau. Um cinco num dia bom.
Did you give her Honest-Ease?
Deram-lhe Sinceridrina?
No, I would have to ask. You know.
Nדo sem permissדo.
I'm just kind of a bitch.
Sou um bocado cabra.
Well, then I would like to change my vote to an eight.
Entדo, gostaria de alterar a minha nota para oito.
All right, uh, Jeff, Heather,
Muito bem, Jeff, Heather,
can I have your permission to administer N-40? Drip on?
dדo-me permissדo para administrar N-40? Aceitam?
Acknowledge.
Consinto.
- Uh, yeah. - Heather?
- Sim. - Heather?
God, she's a pain in the ass.
Ela י mesmo chata.
- Acknowledge. - Thank you.
- Consinto. - Obrigado.
Come on, guys. Words, words, words.
Vamos lב. Quero palavras.
Okay, yeah, she's starting to look pretty good.
Pronto, ela comeחa a ficar muito bonita.
Oh, my…
Cיus…
Yeah, she's… She's looking really, really good.
Sim, ela י mesmo…
Heather?
Heather?
Uh, same. Yeah.
O mesmo. Sim.
Okay, pump up the Verbaluce, let's get 'em talking.
Injeta Verbaluce para eles falarem.
Oh, God, she's so beautiful.
Cיus, ela י tדo linda.
Yeah, don't tell us, tell each other.
Nדo nos digam a nףs. Um ao outro.
You're… Oh, my God.
ֹs… Meu Deus!
You're stunning, you're gorgeous.
ֹs deslumbrante, lindo, nדo sei.
Sorry, I didn't see it before.
Desculpa, nדo tinha reparado.
It's okay, you're the most beautiful woman I think I've ever seen in my life.
Nדo faz mal. ֹs a mulher mais linda que jב vi.
Thank you.
Obrigada.
- Yeah. - I could, uh…
- Sim. - Eu podia…
- Yeah? - I could…
- Sim? - Podia…
You could what, Jeff?
Podias o quך, Jeff?
Are we getting this?
Estamos a gravar?
Oh, my God.
Meu Deus!
You okay?
Estדo bem?
What's so funny?
Qual י a piada?
Nothing.
Nada.
I didn't think it was possible.
Nunca pensei que fosse possםvel.
What?
O quך?
I'm liking cuddling.
Gostar de fazer conchinha.
Please send me home with some of this shit.
Por favor, deixa-me levar disto para casa.
Heather…
Heather…
Yes?
Sim?
I love you.
Amo-te.
Holy shit.
Cum caraחas!
I love you too.
Eu tambיm te amo.
N-fucking-40, baby.
A porra do N-40!
Yeah, God damn, we're good.
Sim, raios, somos bons!
The love drug.
A droga do amor.
Gold star?
Estrela dourada?
Not yet, not yet. No, no.
Nדo, ainda nדo.
We're less interested in what we just saw than the residual effect.
Estamos mais interessados no efeito residual.
I realize you're stretched thin, but I need you to observe these two.
Sei que estבs cheio de trabalho, mas preciso que os observes.
After they come down, in the next hours, days, do they seek contact?
Vך se se procuram nas prףximas horas ou dias apףs o efeito passar.
Profess feelings when they're in the same room?
Se professam sentimentos quando se cruzarem.
Do they communicate non-verbally? Look for isopraxisms.
Comunicam de forma nדo verbal? Procura isopraxismos.
Uh, mirrored behaviors.
Espelhamentos.
People in love unconsciously mimic each other's actions.
Gente apaixonada imita-se inconscientemente.
They scratch their faces, fiddle with their hair at the same time.
Coחam a cara e mexem no cabelo ao mesmo tempo.
It's like their bodies can't help themselves.
Nדo conseguem evitar.
So watch Jeff and Heather.
Observa o Jeff e a Heather.
I want to know. I want to know, does love…
Eu quero saber se o amor…
Does this love last?
Este amor י duradouro?
Hey, guys, thank you.
Malta, obrigado.
Thank you very much, no kidding. We couldn't do it without you.
Muito obrigado. Nדo terםamos conseguido sem vocךs.
Remember, what you're feeling,
O que estדo a sentir,
the sometimes disquieting transitions are natural.
as transiחץes por vezes inquietantes sדo normais.
We're bringing you back to baseline. More to come.
Vדo voltar ao normal. Depois hב mais.
Am I back on snack?
Volto א cozinha?
You don't wanna know, trust me.
Nדo queiras saber, acredita.
Me and the girls at the group home,
Eu e as miתdas do abrigo
we swiped lottery tickets from convenience stores,
roubבvamos raspadinhas nas lojas de conveniךncia
scratched them a hundred at a time.
e raspבvamos cem de cada vez.
It looked like we were doing honest work, you know, dirt under our nails.
Atי parecia trabalho honesto, com sujidade nas unhas.
It's not like we thought stealing was bad, right?
Nדo vםamos roubar como uma coisa mב, percebes?
No one needed it more than us 'cause we had nothin'.
- Era pura necessidade. Nדo tםnhamos nada. - Pois.
This one Christmas Eve, we're drivin' through neighborhoods,
Numa vיspera de Natal, saםmos de carro pelos bairros. Estavam todos na igreja.
We're breaking windows,
Partimos janelas,
stealing presents from under people's Christmas trees…
roubבmos prendas que estavam debaixo das בrvores.
Know what happens the next morning?
Toma. E na manhד seguinte?
We're openin' up other people's sweaters, The Grinch comes on TV.
Desembrulhבvamos camisolas e passa o Grinch na televisדo.
Man.
- Caramba! - A parte em que ele devolve as prendas?
- I felt so bad. - Yeah, I bet.
- Senti-me tדo mal. - Aposto.
I cried like a little punk-ass.
Chorei como uma choninha.
Afternoon, kids.
Boa tarde, crianחas.
Sarah, you know Jeff. Jeff, you know Sarah.
Sarah, Jeff, jב se conhecem.
Hey.
Olב.
As you know, we're wall-to-wall today.
Como sabem, hoje temos um dia cheio. O chefe estב a pressionar.
- So, if it's cool... - Acknowledge.
- Se nדo se importam… - Consinto.
Yeah, fine. Acknowledge.
Sim, estב bem. Consinto.
I can't watch.
Nדo consigo ver.
Sarah or the double dose?
A Sarah ou a dose dupla?
Sarah on the double dose.
A Sarah com a dose dupla.
We're all here by choice, Mark.
Estamos cב por opחדo prףpria.
Is she…
Ela estב…
Yeah, I think so.
Acho que sim.
Yes! Yes!
Sim!
What's up, Ray?
Como vai isso, Ray?
Someone wrote in shit on the bathroom stall doors, that's what.
Escreveram com merda nas portas da casa de banho.
Gross.
Que nojo.
I'll find out who's shit-finger. Hope it ain't you.
Vou encontrar o dedo borrado. Espero que nדo seja o teu.
It's not.
Nדo י.
Damn, I will never be as good at anything as you are with that.
Nunca serei tדo bom em nada como tu יs com isso.
- You like that? - Yeah.
- Gostas? - Sim.
Hey, is there a drug to make you forget shit?
Hב alguma droga para nos esquecermos de merdas?
Yeah, it's called old age.
Sim, chama-se velhice.
I'm looking forward to it.
Mal posso esperar.
How you feeling?
Como te sentes?
I'm all right. A little sore.
Estou bem. Um bocado dorido.
It must've felt pretty good at the time though.
Na altura deve ter sabido muito bem.
Yeah.
Sim.
I'm fine. Thanks, though.
Nדo י preciso, mas obrigado.
Hey, uh, do me a favor.
Olha, faz-me um favor.
While we're at it, try not to let the girls touch your MobiPak.
Tenta que as gajas nדo toquem no Mobipack.
And don't… And don't touch theirs. Okay?
E nדo toques no delas. Estב bem?
I know it gets crazy in there, but they're not made for jostling,
Sei que as coisas se descontrolam, mas eles sדo sensםveis
they can flood.
e podem verter.
You could lose control.
Podes perder o controlo.
Cool.
Na boa.
Uh, hey, Mark?
Mark?
Yeah?
Sim?
Can you take me off snack?
Podes tirar-me da cozinha?
Was something wrong? Problems with Lizzy?
Houve alguma chatice? Problemas com a Lizzy?
Nah, just, I'm ready for a change.
Nדo, sף queria variar.
Yeah. Okay.
Sim. Estב bem.
Thanks, man.
Obrigado.
God damn it.
Raios partam!
Oh, my God.
Meu Deus!
Lizzy.
Foi a Lizzy.
Is she from Seattle?
Ela י de Seattle?
Prescott, Arizona.
Prescott, Arizona.
Ah, see? Jeff knows.
Estבs a ver? O Jeff sabe. ֹ porreiro quando a malta se conhece.
Speaking of, I saw the box scores this morning.
Por falar nisso, vi as estatםsticas.
You Mariners are on a bit of a streak. We should pipe in a game later, huh?
Os teus Mariners estדo a dar-lhe. Devםamos ver um jogo.
Yeah, that'd be great. Who're they playing?
Seria ףtimo. Vדo jogar contra quem?
Crap. Hey, Mark, return this.
Raios! Mark, devolve isto.
Uh, Jeff, please take a seat. Another full day ahead.
Jeff, senta-te, por favor. Mais um dia cheio.
If you could read the headlines, you can't, but if you could,
Se pudesses ler as manchetes, o mundo precisa da nossa ajuda como nunca.
Now, we got two rooms running today.
Hoje temos duas salas.
Pay no attention to Dave, trust me.
Nדo ligues ao Dave, acredita em mim.
Seriously, trust him.
A sיrio, acredita.
Jeff…
Jeff…
All right. Recognize them?
Muito bem.
That's very funny.
Tem muita graחa.
I'm gonna present you with a choice. This is what I'm after.
Vou dar-te a escolher. ֹ isto que pretendo.
- Mm-hmm. - You see this remote?
Vךs este comando?
Let's say, you can slide this button and Sarah gets some Darkenfloxx,
Digamos que deslizas aqui e a Sarah recebe Agonidrina,
or you could slide this button and Heather gets some Darkenfloxx.
ou podes deslizar aqui e a Heather recebe Agonidrina.
You see? You choose.
Vךs? Escolhes tu.
They have Darkenfloxx in their MobiPaks?
Elas tךm Agonidrina nos Mobipacks?
Excuse me.
Com licenחa.
Hey, Dave, how you feeling?
Dave, como te sentes?
Hungry.
Com fome.
- Could he be shit-finger? - Yeah, maybe.
- O dedo borrado pode ser ele? - Talvez.
All that food's gotta go somewhere.
A comida tem de ir para algum lado.
Where were we? Darkenfloxx.
Onde םamos? Agonidrina.
Mark put it in the ladies' MobiPaks in anticipation of this very study.
O Mark colocou-a nos Mobipacks delas em preparaחדo para este estudo.
That make you feel uncomfortable?
Isso deixa-te desconfortבvel?
A little.
Sim, um pouco.
Yeah? That's okay, it should.
Sim? Tudo bem, י suposto.
But you know as well as I it's just an agitator,
Mas sabes tדo bem como eu que י sף um estimulante
causes no permanent damage. All right?
e nדo causa danos permanentes. Estב bem?
So what's your decision, Jeff?
Qual י a tua decisדo, Jeff?
Is Heather getting the Darkenfloxx or is Sarah?
Quem recebe Agonidrina, a Heather ou a Sarah?
I don't know, I can't say.
Nדo sei dizer.
Can't say or won't say? You kinda have to, you know that.
Nדo sabes ou nדo queres? Sabes que tens de o fazer.
I mean, it's random if I do.
Se o fizer, serב aleatףrio.
You feel your decision would be random?
- A tua decisדo seria aleatףria? - Sim.
This is what we're testing for…
Vou dizer-te o objetivo do estudo.
Is any residual fondness with… With the ladies.
Hב algum afeto residual por elas?
So why don't you tell me how you feel about Heather and Sarah?
Que tal dizeres-me o que sentes pela Heather e pela Sarah?
How I feel?
O que sinto?
Maybe some Verbaluce?
Um pouco de Verbaluce?
No.
Nדo. Nדo י que eu goste de ambas ou que goste mais de uma do que da outra.
It's just, I… I just don't really feel anything towards either of them, you know?
ֹ sף que nדo sinto nada em relaחדo a nenhuma delas, entendes?
I mean, I can remember feeling a certain way towards 'em,
Lembro-me de sentir coisas em relaחדo a ambas,
but that's all kind of hazy and worn off now.
mas jב estב tudo muito vago e quase esquecido.
And why such reluctance to the Darkenfloxx then?
Entדo, porquך tanta relutגncia com a Agonidrina?
Because I was a part of I-16.
Porque eu participei no I-16.
I mean, I know what it's like, and you know what it's like.
Eu sei como י e tu tambיm sabes.
- It's… - Yeah.
- ֹ… - Sim.
It's… It's horrible.
ֹ horrםvel.
And I just… I don't want to do that to anyone.
E nדo quero fazer isso a ninguיm.
Look, I don't know. It's random.
Olha, nדo sei. ֹ aleatףrio.
Okay. I'll tell you what.
Muito bem. Fazemos o seguinte.
I'm giving the Darkenfloxx to Heather. Okay?
Vou dar a Agonidrina א Heather. Estב bem?
Actually, I'm gonna give it to Sarah.
Na verdade, vou dב-la א Sarah.
All right, Jeff, you've convinced me.
Pronto, Jeff, convenceste-me.
It would to you be random, you truly have no preference.
Seria mesmo aleatףrio. Nדo tens preferךncia.
My preference is that nobody gets it.
Prefiro que ninguיm receba isso.
That makes two of us.
Jב somos dois.
Three.
Trךs.
See what we just did.
Vךs o que conseguimos? Com a tua ajuda, aprendemos muito mais sobre o N-40.
"Luvactin," working title.
"Amamina", tםtulo provisףrio.
So, no one's getting Darkenfloxx?
Entדo, ninguיm vai receber Agonidrina?
Not today.
Hoje nדo. Mas precisamos de compreender melhor o N-40.
For instance, uh, what's the drug's duration?
Por exemplo, quanto tempo dura o efeito?
What's the variable effect of its dosage?
Quanto varia o efeito face א posologia.
You and Sarah were on double the dose of you and Heather
Com a Sarah, a dose foi o dobro da Heather,
and yet your feelings for the two women are largely the same.
mas os sentimentos por ambas sדo basicamente iguais.
Don't you find that interesting?
Nדo achas interessante?
Yeah.
Sim.
Hey, uh, I, uh… I'm not one to bring Darkenfloxx in any conversation,
Nדo me agrada puxar o tema da Agonidrina,
but we have to know more about N-40. It could be a game-changer, Jeff.
mas temos de saber mais sobre o N-40. Pode mudar tudo, Jeff.
The work we do could help millions of people.
Este trabalho poderia ajudar milhץes de pessoas.
You ever loved?
Jב amaste alguיm?
Yeah.
Sim.
Yeah, you were lucky. Not everyone can.
Tiveste sorte. Nem todos conseguem.
You know that loneliness is as lethal as smoking 15 cigarettes a day?
Sabes que a solidדo י tדo letal quanto fumar 15 cigarros por dia?
Look it up.
Podes pesquisar.
Imagine if we could destroy all the world's cigarettes.
Imagina se pudיssemos destruir todos os cigarros do mundo.
We'd have people everywhere loving, being loved, capable of love,
Terםamos pessoas a amar, a serem amadas, capazes de amar,
and who would've made that possible?
e quem teria possibilitado isso?
- Gold star for me. - Yeah.
Estrela para mim.
Okay. Thank you, ladies.
Muito bem. Obrigado, senhoras.
Excuse you, Jeff.
Podes ir, Jeff.
Hey. Everything okay?
Espera.
Yeah.
Sim.
They don't know how close they came to getting Darkenfloxxed.
Elas nem imaginam que quase receberam Agonidrina.
Yeah, I know. I get it.
Sim, eu entendo.
But listen, man, think if you'd had the benefit of one of our products
Mas pensa que se tivesses o benefםcio dos nossos produtos
before your fateful night…
antes da tua noite fatםdica…
What is it you want, Jeff, more than anything in the world?
O que queres, Jeff, mais do que tudo no mundo?
To go back.
Voltar.
What you want is redemption.
O que queres י redenחדo.
And this is how you're gonna find it.
E י assim que a vais encontrar.
Yeah, thanks.
Sim, obrigado.
Hey.
Olב.
Meatball?
Almפndega?
Yeah, sure.
Sim, claro.
Ah, sorry.
Desculpa.
It's all right. I suck at this game anyway.
Nדo faz mal. Sou pיssimo neste jogo.
- Hey, I wanted to... - Hey, Jeff.
- Eu queria… - Jeff.
Ah, Free Fridays.
Sextas Livres.
Lucky.
Sortudo.
Say hi to the missus for me.
Dב cumprimentos meus א senhora.
Hi, it's Emma. Leave a message or don't.
Olב, fala a Emma. Deixe mensagem, ou nדo.
Hey, babe, you're probably getting sick of me leaving these things for you,
Olב, querida. Deves estar farta de que eu te deixe estas coisas,
but I just wanted to tell you the usual that I miss you and I'm sorry.
mas sף queria dizer o costume, que tenho saudades e que lamento.
Something else I wanna tell you too.
Tambיm te queria dizer outra coisa.
She kinda reminds me of you a little bit.
De certa forma, recorda-me de ti.
So maybe I'll finally stop bugging you.
Talvez eu pare finalmente de te chatear.
This'll be my last, "I'm sorry."
Este serב o meu תltimo "lamento".
Yeah, come in.
Sim, entre.
Merry Christmas, Lizzy.
Feliz Natal, Lizzy!
- Have you been a nice girl? - This is…
- Portaste-te bem? - Isto י…
This is Santa?
Isto י o Pai Natal?
Hello!
Olב!
Thought this might cheer us up.
Achei que talvez nos alegrasse.
- Merry Christmas.
Feliz Natal.
God.
Meu Deus!
It's not actually Christmas though, is it?
Nדo י mesmo Natal, pois nדo?
October?
Outubro?
- Yeah, just a guess. - Okay.
- ֹ sף um palpite. - Certo.
I'd play "Jingle Bells," but we get this instead.
Em vez de "Jingle Bells", temos isto.
You know what? I'll make some eggnog.
Sabes que mais? Vou fazer eggnog.
- Mm. - Yeah?
- Sim? - O Pai Natal gosta.
Hey, Rogan.
Olב, Rogan.
Go fuck yourself.
Vai-te foder.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Nדo.
- No way, guys. Come on. - Just relax.
- Nem pensem. Vב lב. - Calma.
We know what it does. Okay? We've all seen what it does.
Sabemos o que faz. Estב bem? Jב todos vimos o que faz.
It's already proven. This isn't some type of skin show.
Jב estב comprovado. Isto nדo י um striptease.
Tell 'em, Rogan.
Diz-lhes, Rogan.
I don't know what you're talkin' about. But fuck all y'all.
Nדo sei do que estבs a falar, mas vדo-se foder todos.
- He has a future in greeting cards. - I can fuckin' hear you!
- O tipo י um poeta. - Eu consigo ouvir-vos!
Guys, listen, listen to me, okay?
Malta, escutem-me, sim?
I've never been with a… Uh…
Nunca estive com um…
No offense, man. If you have, that's fine.
Nדo leves a mal. Se o fizeste, tudo bem.
It's not my thing. Whatever.
Nדo י a minha onda. Adiante. Olha, Mark, eu nדo recuperei.
I asked for cream, nobody brought me cream.
Pedi pomada e ninguיm me trouxe.
So I'm not doing this. I won't.
Portanto, nדo vou fazer isto.
No, I'm not. No! No! No! No!
Nדo, nדo o farei. Nדo!
I'm not, I won't. I won't acknowledge.
Nדo o farei. Nדo consentirei.
Jeff, chill pill. It isn't what you think. No romance novels today.
Jeff, tem calma. Nדo י o que pensas. Hoje nדo hב romances.
Your loss.
Tu י que perdes.
Funny.
Engraחadinho.
That's it, guys. Thanks.
ֹ tudo. Obrigado.
What the fuck was that about?
Que porra foi aquela?
Ping-pong tournament set for Saturday.
O torneio de pingue-pongue י no sבbado. Para participarem, falem com o Ray.
- Oh, hi, Jeff. - Hey, Heather.
- Olב, Jeff. - Heather.
It's not the time.
Nדo י o momento.
Did Mr. Abnesti ask you who to Darkenfloxx, me or Rogan?
O Sr. Abnesti perguntou-te a qual dos dois querias dar Agonidrina?
- He did present me with that dilemma... - Heather.
- Ele apresentou-me esse dilema… - Heather.
Did you recently have sex with Rogan in addition to me
Fizeste recentemente sexo com o Rogan, alיm de mim,
and fall in love with him like you did with me?
e tambיm te apaixonaste por ele?
Jeff, come on.
- Jeff, vב lב. - ֹ uma descriחדo precisa da situaחדo.
- Heather, put a sock in it. - Okay.
- Heather, mete uma rolha. - Estב bem.
Jeff, what are you doing?
Jeff, o que estבs a fazer?
Now she's looking for her sock. You get very literal on Verbaluce.
Vai usar a meia como rolha. O Verbaluce torna-nos literais.
Yes, I'm aware. Thank you. Show yourself out, close the door.
Eu sei. Obrigado. Podes sair e fecha a porta.
- Okay. - Well done.
- Certo. - Terminבmos.
Please show yourself out, thank you.
Podes sair, obrigado.
- Jesus Christ, Jeff. It's... - Wow. Yeah.
- Caramba, Jeff, י… - Sim.
What's going on, huh?
O que se passa?
- So everybody's just fucking everyone? - Language.
- Andam todos a foder com todos? - Vך como falas.
Everyone's fucking everyone.
Andam todos a foder.
- Relax. - And being asked to Darkenfloxx everyone.
- Calma. - E dדo Agonidrina uns aos outros.
It's experimental design.
ֹ um formato experimental. Quem faz as regras י o Comitי de Protocolo.
Here you go. Huh?
Toma lב.
You think I want to do this?
Achas que quero fazer isto?
Let me close the door.
Vou fechar a porta.
Mark, I mean, look, man,
Mark, olha,
I've been on some crazy-ass project teams, right?
eu participei em projetos absurdos, percebes?
But this one… Yeah, this one doesn't feel right.
Mas este… Pois, este nדo parece certo.
Jeff, you know, I sympathize, but only to a point.
Jeff, eu entendo, mas sף atי certo ponto.
I gotta take off my friendship hat for a second and remind you,
Vou esquecer a amizade por um instante e relembrar-te
your presence in this facility,
de que a tua presenחa aqui,
while technically a punishment, is a privilege. Is it not?
embora seja uma puniחדo, tambיm י um privilיgio. Nדo י?
You applied for it, you were approved for it.
Candidataste-te e foste aprovado.
You could as easily be at State with the general pop
Podias estar na prisדo estadual com os outros
and you would be playing pitch-and-catch,
e a dar o cu a tipos como o Rogan.
And secondly, our open-door policy is my greatest pride.
Segundo, a polםtica de abertura י o meu maior orgulho.
I can come visit you, you can visit me.
Posso ir visitar-te e tu a mim.
Even in my quarters or up here in the Spider head.
No meu quarto ou aqui na Cabeחa da Aranha.
No other penal institution in the world boasts such a respectful relationship
Nenhuma outra instituiחדo penal fomenta tanto respeito
between the jailer and the jailed.
entre carcereiro e encarcerado.
No bars, no guards, that's only possible in a culture of mutual respect.
Nדo hב grades nem guardas. Sף י possםvel numa cultura de respeito mתtuo.
Okay? Mutual respect. I don't burst in on you, do I?
Estב bem? Respeito mתtuo. Nדo invado o teu espaחo, pois nדo?
- No.
- Nדo.
So, you don't burst in on me. We must honor that or it's my ass.
Por isso, nדo invades o meu. Ou respeitamos isso ou estou feito.
Doors close, locks go on,
Com as portas trancadas, somos iguais ao resto, percebes?
Yes.
Sim.
Jesus, is it all that terrible here?
Credo! Isto י assim tדo horrםvel?
The food, the ping-pong, arcade games,
A comida, o pingue-pongue, os jogos de salדo,
freedom within reason to move around as you please.
a liberdade de circulaחדo na medida do razoבvel.
I've insisted on that for you.
Insisti para teres isso.
I've flirted with violating state compliance standards,
Arrisquei violar os protocolos estaduais com grande risco pessoal.
- Hmm? Come on, say something. - He's right.
- Vב, diz algo. - Ele tem razדo.
At least you could return the sentiment.
O mםnimo que podias fazer era retribuir.
It's the least you could do.
Era o mםnimo.
I'm sorry.
Peחo desculpa.
Okay? I…
Estב bem? Eu…
It's just, all this talk of Darkenfloxx, it gets me on edge. Okay?
Esta conversa da Agonidrina deixa-me nervoso. Estב bem?
I hate this, Jeff and I'm sorry. Okay?
Odeio isto, Jeff. Desculpa, sim?
I just…
ֹ que…
I need to know if we can count on you.
Preciso de saber se podemos contar contigo.
Can we count on you in the future to honor our arrangement?
Vais cumprir o nosso acordo futuramente?
Hey, Sarah.
Olב, Sarah.
This time, next week, we'll have our last gold star, don't you think?
Para a semana, teremos a תltima estrela dourada, nדo achas?
Mark, smile once in a while, okay? We're changing the world.
Mark, sorri de vez em quando. Estamos a mudar o mundo.
Yeah.
Sim.
Not you too.
Tu tambיm, nדo.
Listen, Darkenfloxx is a tool, okay?
Escuta, a Agonidrina י uma ferramenta.
It's gonna help us figure out the important shit.
Vai ajudar-nos a perceber as merdas importantes.
This time, next week, right back in the drawer, I promise.
Para a semana, deixamos de a usar, prometo.
Yeah? What?
Estב bem? O que foi?
Well, just something Jeff said about wanting a drug to forget.
ֹ sף algo que o Jeff disse sobre querer uma droga para esquecer.
You need to relax, okay?
Tens de descontrair, sim?
Enjoy your weekend, Mark.
Aproveita o fim de semana, Mark.
Hit the mainland, clear your head.
Sai da ilha, vai espairecer. Precisas. Precisamos os dois.
Maybe wings, beer, Skee-Ball, whatever you kids are into?
Umas asinhas, cerveja, Skee-Ball, o que os putos gostam?
Yeah, um… Oh, I think Skee-Ball.
Sim, Skee-Ball parece-me bem.
Bye, Mark.
Adeus, Mark.
Holy fucking shit.
Cum caraחas!
I mean, it's hard to describe without Verbaluce,
ֹ difםcil descrever sem Verbaluce,
but just imagine the worst you've ever felt times ten,
mas multiplica o pior que jב te sentiste por dez
and even that doesn't even come close to it, honestly, I mean…
e nem isso se aproxima do que estou a dizer.
I felt like I was on fire.
Senti que estava a arder.
I wished I was on fire.
Desejei estar a arder.
I would have set myself on fire to make it stop. It's horrible.
Ter-me-ia incendiado para que parasse. ֹ horrםvel.
So they give this Darkenfloxx to someone?
Dדo a tal Agonidrina a alguיm?
I mean, not this time.
Quer dizer, nדo desta vez.
Well, that's good.
Isso י bom.
Jesus, you're shaking.
Cיus, estבs a tremer!
You're a good guy.
ֹs um bom tipo.
Look, I heard from Mark that you asked to be taken off snack.
Olha, eu soube pelo Mark que pediste para sair da cozinha.
I assume that meant away from me, right?
ֹ para te distanciares de mim, certo?
It's 'cause of, uh…
Por causa da…
Emma?
Da Emma?
Yeah.
Sim.
No, she's…
Nדo, ela…
She's moved on.
Ela virou a pבgina.
It just helps to hear her voice sometimes.
Mas, por vezes, ajuda ouvir a voz dela.
Yeah, I know. Of course, I get it, you know.
Sim, claro, eu entendo.
This place can really mess with your head.
Este sםtio consegue afetar-nos a cabeחa.
I mean, they've been testing me up and down a lot weirder stuff than usual.
Tךm-me testado a torto e a direito. Coisas mais estranhas do que o costume.
It's just been really tough lately.
Ultimamente tem sido duro.
Sometimes, it's hard to remember who I was before I came in here.
Por vezes, י difםcil lembrar-me de quem era antes de vir para cב.
But, Lizzy…
Mas, Lizzy…
When I'm with you…
Quando estou contigo…
That's the only time I really feel like myself.
… י a תnica altura em que me sinto eu prףprio.
Hands up, Mark. Come on. There you go.
Levanta as mדos, Mark. Isso mesmo.
So, I had a big idea for G-46.
Tive uma grande ideia para o G-46.
Oh, yeah? What, Laffodil?
Sim? O Risodil?
Yes, uh, we sell it to comedy clubs.
Sim, vendemo-lo a clubes de comיdia.
That's a little idea, Mark. No offense.
Isso י uma ideia pequena, Mark. Nדo leves a mal.
Offense kind of taken.
Levo um bocado a mal.
What do I keep saying to you, huh?
O que te digo sempre?
I don't know, "Shut up, Mark"?
"Cala-te, Mark"?
I say you gotta think huge.
Que tens de pensar em grande.
You look at the world through the wrong end of binoculars.
Vךs o mundo com binףculos ao contrבrio.
That's weird. Don't be weird.
ֹ estranho. Nדo sejas estranho.
Hey, uh, what time do we start?
A que horas comeחamos?
Ten minutes.
Em dez minutos.
Why don't you hit me? We got time.
Dב-me uma dose. Temos tempo.
Come on, hit me. Let's go.
Vב, dב-me uma dose. Vamos lב.
- Two? - Uh, make it three.
- Duas? - Podem ser trךs.
Remember, at least 12 hours apart.
Lembra-te, 12 horas de intervalo, pelo menos.
Yeah, I've heard the dosing schedule. Thank you.
Eu conheחo a posologia. Obrigado.
Say it. Come on, you've been wanting to for a while.
Diz lב. Hב algum tempo que queres dizer.
Best shot.
Manda vir.
You of all people...
Tu, mais do que todos…
Should understand the risks?
Devia compreender os riscos? ֹ esse o meu objetivo.
- We can assess risks without taking them. - Oh, can I?
- Podemos avaliar riscos sem os correr. - Posso?
Someone has to answer for our products, Mark.
Alguיm tem de responder pelos produtos. Nדo te ocorreu isso?
Life out there is not life in here, okay? Shit is messy.
A vida lב fora nדo י como aqui. ֹ tramada.
It's out of our control. This is new frontier stuff here.
Estב fora do nosso controlo. Isto י revolucionבrio.
And when, not if, when one of our compounds falls on its face,
E quando um dos nossos compostos falhar, e vai falhar,
one of us has to stand in front of a bereaved loved one,
um de nףs terב de encarar um familiar enlutado,
or Mike Wallace, or God forbid, a jury, and answer for what we do.
o Mike Wallace ou um jתri e responder pelo que fazemos.
What we made and bottled and named and sold.
Pelo que produzimos, nomeבmos e vendemos. Vais ser tu?
No, it's gonna be the guy who can say,
Nדo, serב o tipo que pode dizer:
"You're right I stand behind our shit. I've taken it myself."
"Podem crer que defendo isto. Eu prףprio tomei."
Mike Wallace is dead.
O Mike Wallace morreu.
Really? Hard to keep track. Ed Bradley then.
A sיrio? ֹ difםcil acompanhar. O Ed Bradley.
Also dead.
Tambיm morreu.
Morley Safer?
O Morley Safer?
Shit. Better to think someone's dead, and find out they're alive.
Merda! ֹ melhor pensar que morreram e descobrir que estדo vivos.
Yeah, when you first hired me...
Quando me contrataste…
Yeah, you disapproved. Duly noted.
Sim, eras contra. Registado.
Hey, Jeff, how are you?
Olב. Jeff, como estבs?
- Hey. - Sorry, I didn't mean to…
- Olב. - Desculpem, nדo queria…
That's cool. Maybe a bit of advance notice next time.
Tudo bem. Para a prףxima, avisa antes.
Sure.
Claro.
Yeah, shall we?
Vamos?
Nobel Prize ain't gonna win itself.
O Prיmio Nobel nדo se ganha sozinho.
Mark?
Mark?
I'm gonna freshen up, so be down in a second.
Vou trocar-me e jב volto.
Shit.
Merda!
- Is Heather… - On her way.
- A Heather… - Estב a caminho.
Beautiful people get away with too much.
As pessoas bonitas fazem o que querem. Digo isso com conhecimento de causa.
Heather, thanks for joining us. Be right with you.
Heather, obrigado por vires. Jב falo contigo.
All right, uh, Jeff, I want to start by apologizing.
Muito bem, Jeff, quero comeחar por pedir desculpa.
No, look, I shouldn't have walked in on you.
Nדo, eu nדo devia ter aparecido sem avisar.
Oh. No, not that. Uh…
Nדo י isso.
Remember the other day when I asked you
Lembras-te de quando te perguntei
which girl to give the Darkenfloxx to and you said neither?
a qual dar a Agonidrina e disseste a nenhuma?
Yeah.
Sim.
That was good enough for me, but apparently not the Protocol Committee.
Isso bastou-me, mas nדo ao Comitי de Protocolo.
- Mm-hmm. - Three Horsemen of Anality.
Trךs Cavaleiros da Canalhice.
They're not convinced you don't have residual feelings
Ainda nדo acreditam que nדo sintas nada pela Heather e pela Sarah.
So, unfortunately today we gotta do a kind of a confirmation trial.
Infelizmente, hoje teremos de fazer um ensaio de confirmaחדo.
This time per the Protocol Committee, Mark,
Desta vez, segundo o Comitי de Protocolo, Mark,
which the Protcom felt was, they say, "too subjective,"
algo que o Comitי achou "demasiado subjetivo",
we're gonna give the girl the Darkenfloxx and then see what you say.
vamos dar Agonidrina א rapariga e ver o que dizes.
Once again on some Verbaluce.
Mais uma vez, sob efeito de Verbaluce.
You refreshed his MobiPak? His quantities good?
O Mobipack tem quantidade suficiente?
They are. Plus I already told you they are.
Sim. Jב te tinha dito que sim.
And what about Heather's?
E o da Heather?
You stood right there and watched me, Steve.
Estavas lב e viste, Steve.
That I did, Mark.
Pois foi, Mark.
Sorry, Jeff, we're a little tense today.
Desculpa, Jeff. O ambiente estב tenso.
Not an easy day and everyone's a little bit uncomfortable about this.
Nדo י um dia fבcil e estamos todos desconfortבveis com isto.
I don't want you to Darkenfloxx Heather.
Nדo quero que deem Agonidrina א Heather.
Okay, good start.
Bom comeחo.
Uh, is that because you love her? Feelings of love?
Porque a amas? Sentimentos de amor?
No, I mean, I already told you that.
Nדo, jב te tinha dito.
Yeah, uh, and I agreed,
Sim, e concordei,
but is this confirmation trial about what you and I want?
mas este ensaio de confirmaחדo י sobre o que tu e eu queremos?
Not so much.
Nem por isso.
What it is about is about us recording what you say
Trata-se de registarmos o que tu dizes
as you observe Heather getting Darkenfloxxed
ao veres a Heather a receber Agonidrina durante cinco minutos.
One five-minute trial. Okay?
Um ensaio de cinco minutos. Estב bem?
So, here we go with the Verbaluce.
Pronto, comecemos com o Verbaluce.
Drip on, Jeff?
Aceitas, Jeff?
Oh, come on, Jeff.
Vב lב, Jeff.
You should be flattered. Did we choose Rogan?
ֹ uma honra. Escolhemos o Rogan?
You're afraid of Rogan.
Tens medo do Rogan.
Yeah, Rogan could kill you with a box of Kleenex.
Sim, o Rogan pode matar-te com uma caixa de lenחos.
But no, we deemed your level of speaking more commensurate with our data needs.
Mas nדo, considerבmos a tua eloquךncia mais adequada ao que precisamos.
Drip on?
Aceitas?
God, did you even know Heather's story?
Conheces a histףria da Heather? Legalmente, nדo podes conhecer.
But does it involve whiskey, gangs, patricide? I can't say.
Envolve uםsque, gangues, parricםdio? Nדo posso dizer.
But can I imply that her past did not exactly include a dog named Lassie
Mas posso insinuar que o passado dela nדo incluםa um cדo chamado Lassie
and a lot of family talks about the Bible while grammy sat doing macramé?
e conversas sobre a Bםblia enquanto a avף fazia macramי?
Can I suggest if… Mark, empty.
Posso sugerir… Mark, estב vazio.
Can I suggest if you knew Heather's past,
Se conhecesses o passado da Heather,
making her feel briefly sad, nauseous, and/or horrified,
fazך-la sentir-se brevemente triste, nauseada ou horrorizada
it might not seem like the worst idea in the world?
talvez nדo parecesse a pior ideia do mundo.
I don't know.
Nדo sei.
Am I a monster, Jeff?
Sou um monstro, Jeff?
Do I remember birthdays around here?
Lembro-me dos aniversבrios?
Who took you up in his seaplane that one time?
- Quem te levou no hidroaviדo? - Tu.
did a certain individual rush to pick up a prescription,
uma certa pessoa foi א pressa aviar uma receita,
paying for it with his own personal money?
pagando-a do prףprio bolso?
- That was nice. - Yeah.
- Foi simpבtico. - Sim.
Seems unprofessional to bring up now.
Nדo parece profissional falar disso.
Come on, Jeff, what do you want me to say here?
Vב lב, Jeff, o que queres que eu diga? As Sextas Livres estדo em risco?
Look, I'm trying to help, Mr. Abnesti.
Estou a tentar ajudar, Sr. Abnesti.
Steve!
Steve!
Can you make a call for me?
Podes ligar-lhes, por mim?
Yeah, all right.
Estב bem.
Let me give it a shot. Okay? BRB.
Vou tentar. Estב bem? Jב volto.
Lizzy.
Lizzy.
Uh, Mr. Abnesti.
Sr. Abnesti.
- My father in the room? - Huh?
O meu pai estב cב?
Who am I kidding? He split when I was eight.
Nדo. Foi-se embora tinha eu oito anos.
Shit, man. I'm sorry.
Porra! Lamento.
We're so happy to have you, Lizzy,
ֹ bom ter-te cב, Lizzy,
and not just 'cause of your culinary skills.
e nדo sף pelos teus dotes culinבrios.
You won best brisket at the Prescott Barbecue Festival,
Ganhaste o prיmio de melhor peito de vaca no Festival de Churrasco de Prescott
three years running?
trךs anos seguidos?
How did you know that?
Como sabia?
- It's my business to know. - Wow.
Saber faz parte do trabalho.
You know, myself,
Eu acho a parte do peito fibrosa, mas…
Okay.
Estב bem.
Did we snag you those copper pots you're after?
Arranjבmos-te os tachos de cobre que querias?
I've been meaning to thank you.
Queria agradecer por isso.
Stop it, stop it, unnecessary.
Para, nדo י preciso. Foste uma boa aquisiחדo.
- It's the least I could do. - Thank you.
- Era o mםnimo. - Obrigada.
In fact, you know, you made me feel, uh…
Na verdade, fizeste-me sentir…
Made me feel a little bit foolish.
Fizeste-me sentir um tolo.
- Foolish? - Yeah.
- Tolo? - Sim.
Just, you get someone's file
Recebes a ficha de alguיm
and, uh, you form these preconceptions, even when you know
e ficas com ideias preconcebidas, mesmo sabendo
there were plenty of circumstances and not so many fair shakes.
que hב imensas circunstגncias e algumas injustiחas.
You still judge.
Mesmo assim, julgas.
Anyone else here, um, know?
Mais alguיm aqui sabe?
Oh, no. Our little secret.
Nדo. ֹ o nosso segredo.
Yeah.
Sim.
This is good. A thousand copper pots for Java like this.
Isto י bom. Este cafי vale mil tachos de cobre.
Or maybe a field trip? An Arizona girl-in-the-sunshine, huh?
Ou talvez uma excursדo? Queres apanhar sol, menina do Arizona?
Hi, Jeff. Uh…
Olב, Jeff.
I'm sorry, man.
Lamento.
Unfortunately, the committee was very firm.
Infelizmente, o Comitי foi intransigente.
They insisted the test must be continued as scheduled.
Insistiram que o teste deve prosseguir conforme planeado.
Otherwise, they're threatening to remove you from this program
Caso contrבrio, ameaחam retirar-te deste programa e mandar-te para a prisדo.
They need you to acknowledge, Jeff.
Eles precisam que consintas, Jeff.
Okay, I'm gonna ask you one last time. Drip on?
Vou perguntar-te uma תltima vez. Aceitas?
Yeah, acknowledge.
Sim, consinto.
Thank you.
Obrigado.
Heather, hello again.
Heather, olב novamente.
Good morning, again.
Bom dia, outra vez.
Drip on?
Aceitas?
Acknowledge.
Consinto.
Okay, Mark.
Muito bem, Mark.
I don't like this.
Nדo gosto disto.
Please. It's hurting.
Por favor. Estב a doer.
What's wrong with me?
O que se passa comigo?
- It can't hurt you. - Shit.
- Nדo te farב mal. - Merda!
Jeff, speak a lot, in detail. Let's make something useful with this.
Jeff, fala muito, com pormenores. Vamos tirar algo תtil disto.
Heather just vomited.
A Heather vomitou.
She appears to be in a highly aversive state.
- Parece estar num estado aversivo. - Recua. O que aconteceu primeiro?
She started to cry.
Ela comeחou a chorar.
She seems confused by how she's feeling.
Parece confusa com o que sente.
Now she's crying harder. She seems unable to sit still.
Chora, mas nדo parece conseguir estar quieta.
And what are you feeling?
E o que sentes tu?
- Melancholy. Culpability. - Oh, no, please.
- Melancolia. Culpabilidade. - Nדo, por favor.
Go on.
Continua.
No, no, no.
Nדo.
All I can think is Heather was once a child.
Sף penso que a Heather jב foi uma crianחa.
Loved by her mother and father…
Amada pela mדe e pelo pai,
…neither foreseeing that one day she might do a terrible thing.
e nenhum deles anteviu que ela um dia faria algo terrםvel.
A thing that would separate her once and for all from love.
Algo que a afastaria para sempre do amor.
Good, go on.
Boa, continua.
Divorce her from joy and cause her unspeakable sadness.
A separaria da alegria e lhe provocaria tristeza indescritםvel.
And do you love her?
E tu ama-la?
Help! Please! Please!
Ajudem! Por favor!
No.
Nדo.
Hang in there, Jeff.
Aguenta aם, Jeff.
Hey, Mark. Any vestige of romantic love
Mark, algum indםcio de amor romגntico no comentבrio verbal do Jeff?
- No. - Great.
- Diria que nדo. - Boa!
Just basic human feeling.
Sדo sentimentos humanos elementares.
Excellent.
Excelente.
Steve.
Steve.
- Mm? - I think it's flooding.
Acho que estב a verter.
Get back!
Para trבs!
Back off.
Corta o fluxo.
I did. The effects not...
Jב cortei. Os efeitos nדo…
Try more red.
Mais vermelho.
Heather is in great torment.
A Heather estב a sofrer muito.
- Back it off. - It's not working.
- Corta. - Estou a tentar. Nדo resulta.
Heather, listen to me. Sit down, don't raise a finger, that's an order.
Heather, escuta. Senta-te e nדo te mexas, י uma ordem.
Get away from me, please!
Afastem-se de mim!
Are you kidding me?
Estדo a gozar?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Estדo a gozar comigo?
Jesus.
Credo!
This is bad. Get in there, go.
Isto י mau. Vai lב.
Shit.
Merda!
Heather's destroying everything within reach.
- A Heather estב a destruir tudo. - Senta-te. ֹ uma ordem.
I'm responsible.
Sou o responsבvel.
Stay the fuck away from me!
Afastem-se de mim!
I facilitated...
Eu viabilizei…
Heather, listen to me, deep breaths, everything's gonna be fine, okay?
Escuta-me, respira fundo e vai ficar tudo bem, estב bem?
Just relax.
Descontrai.
Oh, shit.
Pronto.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Meu Deus!
God damn it, Mark.
Raios partam, Mark!
I don't feel a pulse.
Nדo tem pulso.
What is wrong with you? I told you to back it off.
Qual י o teu problema? Disse para cortares.
What? What? What? I… I did back it off.
O quך? Eu cortei.
- Forget your… - I told you this would happen.
- Esquece… - Disse-te que ia acontecer.
She did not respond to my direct order.
Ela nדo respondeu א minha ordem direta.
You're talking shit.
Sף dizes tretas.
You are afraid to commit… I told you every time, don't hesitate!
Tens medo de te comprometer…
I give an instruction, do what I say!
Dou-te uma instruחדo, faz o que digo!
"Abnesti Pharmaceuticals"?
"Farmacךutica Abnesti"?
Steve, I warned you.
Steve, eu avisei-te.
- You did not. - This is his company.
A empresa י dele.
- I told you. - Do not blame me!
- Eu disse-te. - Nדo me culpes!
You did not listen, I told you. This is your fault.
Nדo me escutaste. A culpa י tua.
I told you. I told you.
Eu disse-te.
- Give me… - You remember that?
- Nדo me dבs… - Lembras-te disso?
"Bingo"?
"Bingo"?
You think I have one job?
Sף tenho um trabalho?
N-40.
N-40.
Can I have your permission to administer N-40? Drip on?
Dדo-me permissדo para administrar N-40? Aceitam?
Acknowledge.
Consinto.
You see this remote?
Vךs este comando?
Let's say, you can slide this button and Sarah gets some Darkenfloxx.
Digamos que deslizas aqui e a Sarah recebe Agonidrina.
I-16.
I-16.
What the hell?
Mas que raio?
- Where are you going? - Shut up, Mark.
- Aonde vais? - Cala-te, Mark.
B-6.
B-6.
I know it gets crazy in there, but they're not made for jostling,
Sei que as coisas se descontrolam, mas eles sדo sensםveis e podem verter.
It's not your fault.
A culpa nדo י tua.
This has gone too far. We need to report this.
Foi longe demais. Temos de comunicar isto.
The time to worry about crossing lines was a lot of lines ago.
O tempo para nos preocuparmos com limites jב passou hב muito.
If anyone finds out what happened to Heather,
Se alguיm descobrir o que aconteceu א Heather, encerram-nos, Mark.
Everything I've accomplished will be lost,
Tudo o que alcancei serב perdido e nדo penses que virדo sף atrבs de mim.
You'll go down too.
Tu tambיm vais א vida.
Yeah.
Pois.
Hey.
Olha.
I'm sorry.
Desculpa.
Okay, this was awful.
Isto foi horrםvel.
But what do I always tell you? Hmm?
Mas o que te digo sempre?
Pressure forms diamonds.
A pressדo faz diamantes.
Yeah.
Sim.
This is fine, okay?
Nדo hב problema, estב bem?
You and I, we're gonna redouble our efforts.
Tu e eu vamos redobrar esforחos.
We're gonna gold star B-6, and we'll change the world, Mark.
O B-6 terב uma estrela dourada e vamos mudar o mundo, Mark.
And Heather? Heather died for the best of causes, okay?
E a Heather? Morreu pela melhor das causas. Estב bem?
Okay.
Estב bem.
"Okay" okay?
Mesmo "bem"?
- Okay. - Yeah?
- Estב bem. - Sim? Mesmo?
Come on, there you are.
Agora sim.
Hey, just go take some time, relax.
Tira um tempo, descontrai.
Whatever helps you forget, get out of here, go on.
O que te ajudar a esquecer. Pץe-te a andar, vai lב.
Is she dead?
Ela estב morta?
She's not the best.
Nדo estב lב muito bem.
That's not fair. Yeah. Yes, she's gone.
Nדo י justo. Sim, ela morreu.
This, uh… You know, this is science, Jeff.
Isto… Isto י ciךncia, Jeff.
And in science, we have to explore the unknown.
E, na ciךncia, temos de explorar o desconhecido.
The unknown can lead to the unforeseen,
Pode levar ao imprevisto e nדo tםnhamos como prever…
Uh, your tone of voice there, Jeff,
O teu tom de voz lב dentro, Jeff…
which I perfectly understand.
Eu entendo perfeitamente.
But be fair. You think what happened today, you think I liked it?
Mas sך justo. Achas que eu gostei do que aconteceu hoje?
I didn't. I'm a person too, you know, I…
Nדo gostei. Tambיm sou uma pessoa.
I have feelings, and no one is more broken up about this than me.
Tenho sentimentos e ninguיm estב mais destroחado que eu.
But in the long run, our work will help ease suffering,
Mas a longo prazo, o nosso trabalho aliviarב sofrimento,
it'll save lives, not just one life, many lives.
salvarב vidas, nדo sף uma, mas muitas vidas.
We're making the world a better place.
Vamos tornar o mundo um lugar melhor.
Are we?
Vamos?
Yes, Jeff, we are.
Sim, Jeff, vamos.
You should be proud.
Devias orgulhar-te.
Personal sadness aside, you did terrific in there.
Tristeza pessoal א parte, estiveste muito bem.
We all did terrific. Heather, especially.
Estivemos todos. Especialmente a Heather.
Right up into the point where she…
Atי ao momento em que ela…
You know, it wasn't her finest moment,
Nדo foi o melhor momento dela, mas esteve muito bem em tudo antes disso
and she'll never be forgotten.
e nunca serב esquecida.
What?
O que foi?
It's just tough.
ֹ duro.
Yeah.
Sim.
Can I get you something for how you're feeling?
Queres algo para o que estבs a sentir?
I swear, G-46 is good shit, right?
Caramba, o G-46 י muito bom, nדo י?
Yeah.
Sim.
Maybe not change-the-world shit, but it's good shit.
Nדo ao ponto de mudar o mundo, mas י muito bom.
It's definitely good shit.
ֹ mesmo bom.
It's hard to have even one sad thought on this stuff.
ֹ difםcil ter um pensamento triste sequer com isto.
What's your worst memory?
Qual י a tua pior recordaחדo?
What?
O quך?
I'm sorry, that's a stupid question.
Desculpa, foi uma pergunta estתpida.
Mine, uh… Mine was… I was…
A minha…
I was eight years old
Eu tinha oito anos
and, uh, my dad told me he was gonna take me to summer camp.
e o meu pai disse-me que me ia levar א colףnia de fיrias.
I was so excited.
Eu estava superentusiasmado.
And he dropped me off, and it turns out it wasn't summer camp,
Ele foi levar-me,
…and I never saw him again.
e nunca mais o vi.
Oh, my God.
Meu Deus!
I'm laughing too.
Tambיm estou a rir.
That's just so terrible, man.
Isto י horrםvel, meu.
It seems funny. Try it.
Parece divertido.
He never came back.
Ele nunca mais voltou.
Not even for a weekend.
Nunca mais voltou. Nem sequer um fim de semana.
I'm actually sorry to hear that, man.
Na verdade, lamento ouvir isso.
Damn.
Raios!
Oh, the dose is too strong.
A dosagem י muito forte.
God.
Cיus!
Man, look at us, huh?
Olha para nףs.
Jeff and Steve.
Jeff e Steve.
Steve and Jeff hanging out.
Steve e Jeff a curtir.
Friends.
Amigos.
What?
O que foi?
Come on, we're up here together.
Vב lב, estamos aqui juntos.
Enjoying the view. That's a friendly thing to do.
A desfrutar da vista. ֹ o que fazem os amigos.
You can… Well…
Tu podes… Bem…
You can walk out that door anytime you want.
Tu podes sair por aquela porta quando quiseres.
I can't.
Eu nדo posso.
No, I can't. Not anymore.
Nדo posso. Jב nדo posso.
What's stopping you?
O que te impede?
The same thing that's stopping you and every decision I've ever made.
A mesma coisa que te impede a ti e todas as decisץes que eu tomei.
The ones that led me here to this place.
As que me trouxeram para aqui, para este lugar.
This is my one true love, Jeff.
Este י o meu verdadeiro amor, Jeff.
And once you fall in love, it's hard to fall back out.
E quando te apaixonas, nדo hב volta.
Okay.
Estב bem.
Jeff and Steve… stuck at summer camp.
Jeff e Steve…
To Jeff and Steve. Not that different.
Um brinde a nףs. Somos pouco diferentes.
Get that fucking thing away from me!
Afastem essa merda de mim!
Lizzy, listen. Deep breaths. Everything's gonna be fine.
Lizzy, escuta. Respira fundo. Vai ficar tudo bem.
Please!
Por favor!
For the record, can you tell us what you're so afraid of?
Para o registo, diz-nos o que te assusta tanto.
Get it the fuck away!
Tirem daqui essa merda!
The Verbaluce isn't doing shit.
O Verbaluce nדo faz nada.
Yeah.
Sim.
This one's a goodie.
Esta י boa.
Phobica.
- Fףbica. - Parem, por favor!
What, like gluten?
Tipo o glתten?
Yeah. Or thinking too much.
Sim. Ou pensar demasiado.
Please, get that fucking thing away from me!
Por favor, afastem essa merda de mim!
I'm worried about post-traumatic stress.
Preocupa-me o stress pףs-traumבtico.
From the stapler?
Por causa do agrafador?
Hey, Lizzy? Lizzy, it's just a stapler.
Lizzy? Lizzy, י sף um agrafador.
Just get away now!
Tirem-no daqui!
What, should we pack it in?
Paramos isto?
Steve, should we pack it in?
Steve, paramos isto?
Yeah, okay.
Sim, estב bem.
The worst one yet. By far.
Foi a pior atי agora. De longe.
How do you feel now?
Como te sentes agora?
Not afraid. Just, uh…
Nדo estou com medo. Sף…
Ashamed?
Envergonhada?
Yeah, I hate that feeling.
Sim, odeio essa sensaחדo.
I couldn't stand feeling that way in front of you.
Nדo aguentava sentir isso diante de ti e pedi para sair da cozinha.
You know, all the years I spent at State.
Passei tantos anos na prisדo estadual.
I come here, and I'm, like…
Venho para cב e…
Is this place even really so much better?
Este sםtio י assim tדo melhor?
I mean, I'd take some beat downs.
Preferia ser espancada
Instead of having a fear of a goddamn stapler.
a ter medo da porra de um agrafador.
Why do we keep saying yes?
Porque dizemos sempre que sim?
Acknowledge, acknowledge, acknowledge.
Consinto, consinto, consinto.
And for what? A private hall pass?
E para quך? Para podermos circular?
A bedroom to ourselves? Copper freakin' pots? I mean…
Termos um quarto individual? Tachos de cobre? Quer dizer…
All the times you've said yes, why did you?
Todas as vezes que consentiste, porque o fizeste?
I guess I felt like I deserved it.
Acho que achava que merecia.
That's what I've been meaning to tell you, Lizzy.
ֹ o que tenho querido dizer-te, Lizzy.
Yeah. I think I might go with them.
Sim. Acho que vou com eles.
Hey. Wait up.
Olhem. Esperem.
She can't live without me.
Ela nדo vive sem mim.
You cool to drive?
Consegues conduzir?
Ice cold.
Na boa.
Oh, Jeff, Jeff, Jeff!
Jeff!
Emma. Come on, baby. Come on.
Emma. Anda, querida. Anda.
Emma! Come on, baby. Come on.
Emma! Anda, querida. Anda.
Hey, babe.
Olב, querida. Deves estar farta de que eu te deixe estas coisas,
but I just wanted to tell you the usual that I miss you…
mas sף queria dizer o costume, que tenho saudades…
And I'm sorry.
… e que lamento.
The mailbox for this customer is full.
A caixa de mensagens estב cheia.
It cannot receive any more messages at this time.
De momento, nדo pode receber mais mensagens.
I'm so sorry.
Lamento imenso.
Two counts, voluntary manslaughter.
Duas acusaחץes de homicםdio culposo.
And that doesn't include Heather.
E isso nדo inclui a Heather.
Don't do that to yourself.
Nדo faחas isso a ti prףprio.
That's not on you.
Nדo tiveste culpa disso.
You did everything you could.
Fizeste tudo o que podias.
No.
Nדo.
I said "acknowledge."
Eu consenti.
And I don't even know why.
E nem sei porquך.
You're a good soul.
ֹs uma alma boa.
We're bad. We're very bad.
Somos maus. Somos muito maus.
For what it's worth, I think we're the least of all evils in here.
Vale o que vale, mas acho que somos o menor dos males aqui.
Yeah? What makes you say that?
Sim? Porque dizes isso?
You hear things.
Ouvem-se coisas.
Oh, you hear things?
Ouvem-se coisas?
Yeah. You know Ray?
Sim. Conheces o Ray?
So, after four times in jail for drugs, Ray went to rehab
Apףs ser preso quatro vezes por drogas, o Ray foi para a reabilitaחדo
and then to what they call a rehab refresh,
e depois para uma reabilitaחדo especial,
which is basically for people who are so immune to rehab,
que י para pessoas que se tornam tדo imunes א reabilitaחדo
- it stops working. - Hmm.
que deixa de resultar.
But he must have been immune to that too, because then came his biggie.
Mas tambיm devia ser imune a isso porque depois veio o maior crime.
Triple murder.
Triplo homicםdio.
Yeah, his dealer, the dealer's sister, and the dealer's sister's boyfriend.
Sim, o traficante, a irmד do traficante
Shit, man.
Porra, pב!
You know Rogan?
Conheces o Rogan?
- Big diesel Rogan. Hell, yeah. - Yeah.
- O armבrio Rogan? Quem nדo conhece? - Sim.
Found his girlfriend cheating on him and threw her out an eight-story window.
encontrou a namorada a traם-lo e atirou-a de uma janela do oitavo piso.
Oh, shit.
Merda!
She did not survive.
Ela nדo sobreviveu.
Crazy.
ֹ de loucos.
Yeah, I don't get it.
Sim, nדo percebo. Como…
You guys are up late.
Estדo a fazer serדo.
Yeah.
Sim.
Cheat day.
Hoje nדo hב dieta.
Oh, Jeff, we may wanna reconsider the community snack bowl, given, uh…
Jeff, nדo comas da tigela comunitבria, dado que…
Shit-finger.
O dedo borrado.
Yeah. Have a wonderful evening.
Sim. Tenham uma boa noite.
- And you.
- Igualmente.
Bingo.
Bingo!
Yes.
Sim.
Okay. I understand. Mm-hmm.
Certo. Eu compreendo.
Thank you.
Obrigado.
Hey, Jeff, thanks for coming in. How're you feeling?
Olב, Jeff, obrigado por teres vindo. Como te sentes?
Uh, I'm good.
Sinto-me bem.
All right, good. Uh, listen, this breaks my heart wide open.
׃timo. Escuta...
But Protcom are insisting on one last trial to establish a baseline.
mas o Comitי insiste num תltimo ensaio para estabelecer uma base de referךncia.
Uh, we…
Nףs…
You have to administer Darkenfloxx to someone you've never shared N-40 with.
Tu tens de administrar Agonidrina a alguיm com quem nunca partilhaste N-40.
Someone who?
Quem?
That's what breaks my heart, Jeff. It really does.
ֹ isso que me deixa destroחado, Jeff.
Eh, Mark, if you would.
Mark, se fazes o favor.
No. Sorry, I can't do it.
Nדo.
Of course you can, Jeff.
Claro que podes. ֹ a תltima vez que alguיm receberב Agonidrina, estב bem?
Yeah, uh, Lizzy doesn't deserve this.
A Lizzy nדo merece isto.
It won't go as far this time. You have my word.
Serב mais comedido, prometo-te.
You're not listening to me.
Nדo me estבs a ouvir.
Jeff, come on. You sound nothing like the guy that first arrived here.
Jeff, vב lב. Nדo pareces nada o tipo que aqui chegou.
That guy would've done anything to make his crime right.
Esse tipo teria feito tudo para se redimir. Quando digo…
Would you just shut up, man?
Podes calar-te?
I'm not doing it.
Nדo o vou fazer.
Calm.
Calma.
Maybe we should take the night. Yeah?
ֹ melhor pararmos esta noite. Sim?
Things always feel better in the morning.
Tudo parece melhor de manhד.
Yeah, sure.
Sim, claro.
Just remember, Jeff, uh, what you did won't have to happen to anyone again.
Lembra-te, Jeff, o que fizeste nדo terב de voltar a acontecer a ninguיm.
Drugs like this will prevent places like this.
Estes fבrmacos evitarדo sםtios como este.
No more damage, no more damaged people.
Nדo haverב mais dor e gente problemבtica.
Only you can prevent another you.
Sף tu podes impedir outro como tu.
Double his dose.
Duplica-lhe a dose.
I know you're struggling, but this will help.
Sei que estבs a sofrer, mas isto vai ajudar.
What's in the red one?
O que tem o vermelho?
It's just a toy.
ֹ sף um brinquedo.
The red one's a placebo. We put it...
- O vermelho י um placebo. Colocamos… - Para.
Just stop.
Jב chega.
There is no Protocol Committee, is there?
Nדo hב Comitי de Protocolo, pois nדo?
This is his company.
Esta empresa י dele.
I saw his letterhead.
Eu vi o papel timbrado.
Abnesti Pharmaceuticals.
Farmacךutica Abnesti.
He's the one in charge
Ele י o responsבvel
and he's naming the drugs using a goddamn Bingo card, Mark.
e nomeia os fבrmacos com um cartדo de bingo, Mark.
What are you doing working at a place like this?
Porque trabalhas num sםtio assim?
I mean, all this talk of N-40, I call bullshit, man.
Esta conversa toda do N-40 י treta.
Abnesti doesn't care about love.
O Abnesti nדo quer saber de amor.
No, he cares about the red one.
Ele quer saber do vermelho.
B-6.
B-6.
How can you go along with this?
Como podes alinhar nisto?
You could work anywhere.
Trabalhas onde quiseres.
Why here? Why him?
Porquך aqui? Porquך ele?
There are so few geniuses.
Nדo hב muitos gיnios.
He promised me we would change the world.
Ele prometeu que mudarםamos o mundo.
I just wanted to help people.
Eu sף queria ajudar pessoas.
You still can.
Ainda podes ajudar.
Hey, Jeff, man of the hour.
Jeff, o homem do momento.
Hope you got some sleep, thought things over, yeah?
Espero que tenhas dormido e pensado melhor. Sim?
Why don't you, uh, take the driver's seat?
Porque nדo te sentas aos comandos?
Mark's out today.
O Mark nדo vem.
He's got a stuffed up nose or something.
Tem o nariz entupido ou lב o que י.
Millennials, huh?
Millennials, nדo י?
Sorry, that's a… It's an unfair word.
Desculpa, י um termo injusto.
You think about it, someone arbitrarily decides
Pensa bem, alguיm decide arbitrariamente
that everyone born between this date and that date, they all act the same.
que os nascidos entre esta e aquela datas agem de forma igual.
It's like a… A horoscope, but stupider.
ֹ como um horףscopo, mas mais estתpido.
You and Mark are nothing alike.
Tu e o Mark sדo diferentes.
I don't know.
Nדo sei.
It was Mark who made me reconsider.
O Mark fez-me reconsiderar.
Well, I'll forgive his sniffles.
Entדo, perdoo-lhe as fungadelas.
Anyway, so it's you and me and Lizzy, makes three.
Bem, יs tu, eu e a Lizzy, somos trךs.
How're you doing, Lizzy?
Como estבs, Lizzy?
Could use some Vitamin D.
Preciso de vitamina D.
We'll get you some sunshine soon enough.
Nדo tarda, poderבs apanhar sol.
All right, Jeff.
Pronto, Jeff.
Dumped the rest. Gone.
Destruם o resto. Foi-se.
Shall we put this thing behind us for good?
Vamos acabar com isto de uma vez?
Fine. Let's do this.
׃timo. Vamos a isto.
Lizzy? Drip on?
Lizzy? Aceitas?
Yeah, acknowledge.
Sim, consinto.
And, Jeff, give Lizzy the Darkenfloxx.
Jeff, dב a Agonidrina א Lizzy.
Sorry.
Desculpa.
The answer is still no.
A resposta continua a ser nדo.
J… Jeff.
Jeff.
Fuck! Fuck, fuck, fuck!
Foda-se!
Okay. What are we up against here, Jeff? Huh?
Muito bem. O que se passa, Jeff?
You think you love her? You don't even know her.
Achas que a amas? Nem sequer a conheces!
I swear, the judgment on display in this fucking building!
Nesta merda de edifםcio sדo todos crםticos!
How about a little share circle, huh? Yeah.
Que tal umas confidךncias? Sim.
Why don't you tell Jeff what you're in for?
Lizzy, dizes ao Jeff porque foste presa?
- I don't care. - That's what love is.
- Nדo quero saber. - Amar nדo י isso?
Getting to know each other. Let's get to know each other.
Conhecermo-nos. Entדo, vamos conhecer-nos.
Doesn't matter. She already told me.
Nדo importa. Jב me contou.
- Oh, did she? - Robbery. Big deal.
- A sיrio? - Roubo. Grande coisa.
Really? Is that what you told him, Lizzy?
Foi isso que lhe contaste, Lizzy? O futuro pai dos teus filhos.
He deserves to know the truth. Tell him. Come on.
Ele merece saber a verdade. Diz-lhe. Vamos lב.
You don't have to.
- Nדo י preciso. - Vamos. Diz-lhe.
Come on, Lizzy, tell him. Tell him.
Vב, Lizzy, diz-lhe. Diz-lhe.
No? All right, I'll do it. Okay?
Nדo? Certo, digo eu. Estב bem?
It's cool. I got your files right here. Let's, uh… Let's see.
Na boa. Tenho aqui a tua ficha. Vejamos.
Yeah? Let's find out about Lizzy.
Sim? Vamos saber mais sobre a Lizzy.
- Get to know each other. - I don't need you to.
- Vamos conhecer-nos. - Nדo י preciso.
- I know who I am and what I've done. - Elizabeth Dianne Harris.
- Sei quem sou e o que fiz. - Elizabeth Dianne Harris.
Born in Prescott, Arizona.
Nascida em Prescott, Arizona.
- Raised in a group home… - I don't need you to. I know who I am.
- Cresceu num abrigo… - Nדo י preciso. Sei quem sou.
I know who I am! I'm the mother who killed her baby.
Sei quem sou! Sou a mדe que matou a filha bebי.
That's who I am, Jeff.
ֹ isso que sou, Jeff.
The mother who forgot her little girl in her car
A mדe que se esqueceu da filha no carro
at a Walmart parking lot in July for three hours…
durante trךs horas num estacionamento do Walmart, em julho…
While I went to work.
… enquanto fui trabalhar.
One count, reckless endangerment. One count, manslaughter
Conduta negligente e homicםdio involuntבrio
of my nine-month-old little girl.
da minha filha de nove meses.
My own…
A minha…
My own flesh and blood.
A minha prףpria filha.
Now, I don't know what kind of sick-ass experiment this is,
Nדo sei que experiךncia doentia י esta,
but whatever he wants you to do to me, come on, let's get on with it, okay?
mas o que ele quer que me faחas, vamos despachar isso, estב bem?
The quicker we get over with, it'll be better for all of us.
Quanto mais depressa, melhor serב para todos.
Come on, man. You can't hurt me.
Vב lב. Nדo me podes magoar.
You can't hurt me.
Nדo me podes magoar.
There's no greater pain than having to wake up
Nדo hב dor maior do que acordar todas as manhדs sem ela.
And I know you think you love me,
E sei que achas que me amas,
but anything in me worth loving died with her long ago.
mas o que merecia ser amado em mim morreu com ela hב muito.
So, come on. Let's do it. Come on. Give it to me.
Vamos lב. Vamos a isso. Injeta.
Fucking give it to me.
Foda-se, injeta!
Give it to me! Fucking do your job, Jeff!
Injeta! Foda-se, faz o teu trabalho, Jeff!
Give it to me!
Injeta!
Give it to me.
Injeta.
Please.
Por favor.
Sorry.
Desculpa.
What's so funny?
Qual י a piada?
Uh, no…
Nדo…
Her sitting in there, this whole thing,
Ela ali sentada, isto tudo,
you with that phone, everyone acting all serious.
tu com esse telemףvel, todos com ar sיrio.
Is it just me who finds this amusing?
Sou sף eu que acho isto divertido?
Yeah.
Sim.
Only you.
Sף tu.
- Give me that. - No.
- Dב-me isso. - Nדo.
Stop it. Stop it, you're scaring me, okay?
Para.
Just stop. Stop. Please don't hurt me.
Para! Nדo me faחas mal, por favor.
Don't… Don't hurt me. Okay?
Nדo me faחas mal. Sim?
God…
Cיus…
Mark spiked my MobiPak.
O Mark manipulou o meu Mobipack.
That's right. He emptied my MobiPak and gave you Darkenfloxx.
Sim. Ele esvaziou o meu Mobipack e deu-te a Agonidrina.
He's coming back here right now with the police.
Estב a voltar com a polםcia.
How could he?
Como foi ele capaz?
He and I… You and I were…
Eu e ele… Tu e eu יramos…
- Can I get you something… - Make it stop!
- Queres algo… - Faz com que pare!
…for how you're feeling?
… para o que sentes?
That was the first thing you said to me…
Disseste-me isso no inםcio.
…the acknowledgement that you needed for the most important study of them all.
O consentimento necessבrio para um estudo importantםssimo.
- And what did we say? - Yes!
- O que respondemos? - Sim!
What were we saying yes to, huh?
O que estבvamos a consentir?
What were we agreeing to put in our bodies every single day?
O que aceitבvamos injetar nos nossos corpos todos os dias?
B-6.
B-6.
It doesn't make you happy or hungry or horny.
Nדo te faz sentir feliz, com fome ou excitado. Faz-te obedecer.
"Laugh, stop laughing. Eat, stop eating. Fuck, stop fucking!"
"Ri, para de rir. Come, para de comer. Fode, para de foder!"
You weren't testing those other drugs. You were testing B-6.
Nדo testavas os outros fבrmacos. Estavas a testar o B-6.
Yeah. Sorry. I'm sorry.
Sim! Peחo desculpa.
I'm sorry.
Peחo desculpa!
What were you gonna call it?
O que lhe ias chamar?
Fine then.
Muito bem.
O-B-D-X.
O-B-D-X.
Obediex.
Obediex.
And it did work.
E funcionou.
Enough for you to live amongst killers. But not enough for a gold star. Why?
Deu para viveres entre assassinos, mas nדo para a estrela dourada. Porquך?
B-6 had to be perfect.
O B-6 tinha de ser perfeito.
The goal wasn't obedience.
A meta nדo era obediךncia.
It was absolute obedience without exceptions.
Era obediךncia absoluta sem exceחץes.
We had to know, could we get you to follow an order
Tםnhamos de saber se vocךs seguiriam uma ordem
antithetical to your deepest values and emotions.
contrבria aos vossos valores e emoחץes mais profundos.
Do the very thing you'd least want to do in the world.
Fazer a coisa que menos queriam fazer no mundo.
Hurt someone you love.
Magoar alguיm que amamos.
B-6 could force you to repeat the precise act you most regretted,
O B-6 poderia forחar-vos a repetir o ato que mais lamentavam,
to harm another, someone you held dear.
o de magoar alguיm que estimavam.
It could force anyone to do anything.
Forחava qualquer um a qualquer coisa.
I trusted you.
Confiei em ti.
We trusted you with our lives!
Confiבmos-te as nossas vidas!
You made us do all this shit to each other,
Obrigaste-nos a fazer estas merdas uns aos outros,
thinking it was our choice, but it was yours.
pensando que era opחדo nossa, mas era tua.
You took away our...
Tiraste-nos o…
Your what? Your free will, Jeff?
O livre-arbםtrio, Jeff?
Can't you picture it?
Nדo consegues imaginar?
A world filled with people who do as they're told.
Um mundo cheio de pessoas que fazem o que lhes mandam.
We'd be selling peace and harmony itself.
Venderםamos paz e harmonia.
The ability to compel people to act on behalf of the greater good.
A capacidade de levar as pessoas a agir pelo bem comum.
Behave, not as they want, but as they damn well should.
De se comportarem como devem, nדo como querem.
No more drunks crashing cars. Husbands killing wives.
Acabavam os acidentes com bךbedos. Maridos que matam esposas.
Kids left at summer camp.
Miתdos abandonados.
What does it matter? B-6 failed.
Que importגncia tem? O B-6 fracassou.
I want you to tell the world what you did to Heather.
Quero que contes o que fizeste א Heather.
Man, I could go to… I could go to prison, it would ruin me.
Eu iria para a prisדo, seria a minha destruiחדo.
Everything I built. I could go to prison, Jeff.
Tudo o que construם. Iria para a prisדo, Jeff.
Jeff and Steve. Not that different.
Jeff e Steve.
Yeah.
Sim.
What's so funny?
Qual י a piada?
You were free to go seven months ago.
Concederam-te liberdade hב sete meses.
And Lizzy, her appeal just fell on very sympathetic ears.
E o recurso da Lizzy obteve muita compreensדo.
She's been free for a week.
ֹ livre hב uma semana.
She's walking out of here. Today.
Ela vai sair daqui.
Open the front door.
Abre a porta da frente.
I'm gonna make sure you never do this to anyone ever again.
Vou garantir que nדo farבs isto a mais ninguיm.
Give me the knife.
Dב-me a faca.
I said… give it to me.
Eu disse… para ma dares.
Why?
Porquך?
Because I told you to, Steve,
Porque eu mandei, Steve,
and because I put enough B-6 in your veins to tame a goddamn lion.
e porque te injetei B-6 suficiente para domar um leדo.
Really works, huh?
Funciona mesmo?
Not when someone has been told to kill the only thing he's ever loved.
Nדo quando mandam alguיm matar a תnica coisa que ele amou.
I learned that from you.
Aprendi contigo.
I just Darkenfloxxed Lizzy. All four vials.
Usei Agonidrina na Lizzy. Os quatro frascos.
I'm so… I'm so sorry.
Lamento muito.
For what?
Pelo quך?
I'm sorry I lied.
Lamento ter mentido.
Lizzy, I love you.
Lizzy, eu amo-te.
Nothing you said or did is gonna change that.
Nada mudarב isso.
Friends and neighbors,
Amigos e vizinhos,
I'm sorry to interrupt, particularly with news like this.
lamento interromper, especialmente com notםcias destas.
We have an attempted escape.
Temos uma tentativa de fuga.
Most of you know Jeff and Lizzy.
Quase todos conhecem o Jeff e a Lizzy.
Most of you know Jeff and Lizzy,
Quase todos os conhecem
and it saddens me to my core that they have misled the authorities
e entristece-me que eles tenham enganado as autoridades
who are on the way here now.
que estדo a caminho.
I explained that that would mean the end of the program
Expliquei que seria o fim do programa
and the comfortable life that it affords us all, but they wouldn't listen.
e da vida confortבvel que nos dב, mas eles nדo me ouviram.
Oh, no.
Nדo.
Do any of you relish the thought of returning to State?
Alguיm gosta da ideia de voltar para a prisדo?
What would you be willing to do to prevent that
O que aceitariam fazer para o impedir
to preserve the noble mission…
e preservar a nobre missדo…
Fuck!
Foda-se!
…to which we've devoted our lives?
… a que dedicבmos as vidas?
Fucking piece of shit!
Que se foda esta merda!
Stop Jeff and Lizzy, not for me, for you.
Detenham o Jeff e a Lizzy, nדo por mim, por vocךs.
Fuck!
Foda-se!
Shit-finger?
Dedo borrado?
I knew it was you, snack man.
Sabia que eras tu.
There they are!
Estדo ali!
I have a key to the pantry.
Tenho a chave da copa.
It has food in it for, like, six months.
Hב lב comida para seis meses.
Awesome. Thanks.
Fixe!
Alpha Whiskey Delta, departing to the north.
A-W-D a descolar para norte.
Alpha Whiskey Delta…
A-W-D a subir, dois mil pיs,
heading east to track zero…
em direחדo a este e rumo zero…
Sorry.
Desculpem.
Zero-nine-zero…
Zero, nove, zero…
Heading zero…
Rumo zero…
Alpha Whiskey Delta, that transmission was gargled.
A-W-D, transmissדo confusa, precisa de assistךncia?
Handle your…
Que se fodam as vossas merdas!
Alpha Whiskey Delta, confirm intentions.
A-W-D. Confirme intenחץes.
We have you bearing northwest, 315, descending below 500 feet.
Aparece a seguir para noroeste, 315,
Glide slope. Pull up.
Inclinaחדo vertical. Subir.
It's beautiful.
ֹ lindo.
Sun feels nice.
O sol sabe bem.
I wish there was a self-forgiveness drug.
Quem dera haver um fבrmaco de autoperdדo.
You take it and everything starts over.
Tomamo-lo e tudo recomeחa.
Everyone you ever loved, you did right by them.
Agiste bem com todos os que amavas.
Treated them like gold and you feel like it's all ahead of me.
Trataste-os extremamente bem e sentes ter a vida pela frente.
This beautiful life, all the pleasures of it.
Uma vida linda e todos os seus prazeres.
The love I could give, the good I could do.
O amor que podia dar, o bem que podia fazer.
But there's no drug like that.
Mas nדo hב um fבrmaco assim.
So, we're gonna have to do it for ourselves.
Teremos de ser nףs a perdoar-nos.